<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<module>
    <id>3</id>
    <title>Rock to Electron</title>
    <content>
        <page>3</page>
        <contentType>video</contentType>
        <thumbnail>Rock_to_Electron.png</thumbnail>
        <url>https://www.youtube.com/v/XwQHfIfS9dM?version=3</url>
        <description>How does a piece of coal become electricity? From the mining, processing, transportation to burning at a power plant, we follow the rock as it becomes a kilowatt.</description>
    </content>
    <content>
        <contentType>image</contentType>
        <thumbnail>Photos.png</thumbnail>
        <caption_image>Rock to Electron image.jpg</caption_image>
        <description>Over 90% of energy in Kentucky comes from coal. How is it possible this rock charges our computers, runs our washing machines, and keeps our lights on? </description>
    </content>
    <content>
        <contentType>text</contentType>
        <thumbnail>More_Info.png</thumbnail>
        <description>  
            Rock to Electron
            
            Can you believe we can get kilowatts from rocks!! A power plant generates
            electricity from a black rock named coal. But how does that process work?
            
            The coal first is mined, prepared and then transported to a power plant. Once it
            arrives at the power plant the coal-fired units produce electricity by burning coal in
            a boiler to heat water to produce steam. The steam, at tremendous pressure, flows
            into a turbine, which spins a generator to produce electricity. The steam is cooled,
            condensed back into water, and returned to the boiler to start the process over.
            
            For example, the coal-fired boilers at TVA’s Kingston Fossil Plant near Knoxville,
            Tennessee, heat water to about 1,000 degrees Fahrenheit (540 degrees Celsius) to
            create steam. The steam is piped to the turbines at pressures of more than 1,800
            pounds per square inch (130 kilograms per square centimeter). The turbines are
            connected to the generators and spin them at 3600 revolutions per minute to make
            alternating current electricity at 20,000 volts. River water is pumped through
            tubes in a condenser to cool and condense the steam coming out of the turbines.
            -The Kingston plant generates about 10 billion kilowatt-hours a year, or enough
            electricity to supply 700,000 homes. To meet this demand, Kingston burns about
            14,000 tons of coal a day, an amount that would fill 140 railroad cars.
            
            Getting electricity from power generating stations to our homes and workplaces is
            quite a challenging process. Electricity must be produced at the same time as it is
            used because large quantities of electricity cannot be stored effectively. High-voltage
            transmission lines (those lines between tall metal towers that you often see along
            the highway) are used to carry electricity from power generating stations to the
            places where it is needed. However, when electricity flows over these lines, some of
            it is lost. One of the properties of high voltage lines is that the higher the voltage, the
            more efficient they are at transmitting electricity — that is, the lower the losses are.
            Using transformers, high-voltage electricity is "stepped-down" several times to a
            lower voltage before arriving over the distribution system of utility poles and wires
            to your home.
            
        </description>
    </content>
    <content>
        <contentType>next</contentType>
        <thumbnail>next.png</thumbnail>
    </content>
</module>
