<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<!-- This is an individual module.  I will comment on the first one only since they are currently all the same.  -->
<!-- You should not change the module id. -->
<module>
    <id>1</id>  <!-- This is the module id...don't change this unless you want to change the order of the modules -->
    <title>Energy 101</title>  <!-- This is the module title...don't change this. -->
    <!-- This is one piece of content in a module.  It can have one of three content types: video, image, or text. -->
    <!-- Each piece of content associated with a module must have its own content section like the one below. -->
    <content>   <!-- This is a video content section -->
        <contentType>video</contentType>    <!-- This must correspond the appropriate type of content...duh lol -->
        <page>1</page>
        <thumbnail>Energy_101.png</thumbnail>    <!-- ADD THIS STILL FRAME AFTER THE VIDEOS ARE UP ON YOUTUBE -->
        <url>https://www.youtube.com/v/DsT7kqp5jTc?version=3</url>  <!-- CHANGE THIS TO THE YOUTUBE URL FOR THE VIDEO -->
        <description>Every day each of us use energy to power our daily activities. We often think that our energy usage doesn’t matter, but it really adds up over time. During a typical day a teenager uses energy from the time they get out of bed until they go back to bed. Let’s add up just how much energy we are using every day. </description>  <!-- DONT CHANGE THIS...UNLESS JULIE CHANGES THE DESCRIPTIONS LATER -->
    </content>  <!-- End video content section -->
    <content> <!-- This is a image content section -->
        <contentType>image</contentType>
        <thumbnail>Photos.png</thumbnail>
        <caption_image>Energy 101 image.jpg</caption_image>
    <!--CHANGE THIS TO THE APPROPRIATE IMAGE FILE NAME -->
        <description>Adding up all the energy you use in a day produces a shocking figure.  As energy use rises, energy supplies fall.  We must conserve resources like coal for the future. </description> <!-- This one should be obvious haha -->
    </content> <!-- End image content section -->
    <content> <!-- This is a raw text content section...I'm not even going to bother with explaing it. -->
        <contentType>text</contentType>
        <thumbnail>More_Info.png</thumbnail>
        <description> 
            Energy 101
            
            We are all incredibly dependent upon energy; we use a lot of it. People don't think
            their personal energy use matters, but does it? How much energy (electric watts)
            do you use in your morning routine before going to school or work? Did you use
            an alarm clock, take a hot shower, use a hair dryer, eat breakfast using a toaster or
            microwave or coffee maker? If so, then you consumed several watts of electricity
            (energy) while doing those simple tasks.
            
            In Kentucky we use a lot of energy in part due to the historically low cost of coal
            generated power.
            
            •   Kentuckians use 55% more electricity than the national average, 3 rd highest
                in energy intensity
            •   Kentucky schools use 7% more electricity per student than the national
                average
            •   State Residential electricity costs have increased 30% more since 2006
            •   Statewide energy demand has increased 2.3% each year. That is twice the
                national average
            
            
            The discussion of energy usage is at the forefront of political and social discussions
            both in our state around the world. The decisions we make today concerning
            energy sources and use will have a big impact on our future.
            </description>
    </content>
    
    <content>
        <contentType>next</contentType>
        <thumbnail>next.png</thumbnail>
    </content>
    
</module>
