<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<module>
    <id>2</id>
    <title>Energy Sources</title>
    <content>
        <page>2</page>
        <contentType>video</contentType>
        <thumbnail>Energy_Sources.png</thumbnail>
        <url>http://youtu.be/bRt2vJEFZAU</url>
        <description>In Kentucky, we use coal for 92% of our energy, but that number is different for every state. Energy can be made from coal, natural gas, oil, hydro and sustainables such as solar, wind or biomass. Each of these energy sources has its own advantages and disadvantages.</description>
    </content>
    <content>
        <contentType>image</contentType>
        <thumbnail>Photos.png</thumbnail>
        <caption_image>Energy Sources image-1.jpg</caption_image>
        <description>Energy surrounds us – it comes from the sun, the wind, and even the movement of water.  We can harness these alternative sources of energy to conserve our nonrenewable fossil fuel reserves. </description>
    </content>
    <content>
        <contentType>text</contentType>
        <thumbnail>More_Info.png</thumbnail>
        <description> 
            Energy Sources
            
            Energy can take the form of electricity, transportation fuels (cars, trucks, airplanes)
            and heating fuels to name a few. Where does energy come from?
            
            Historically, the use of fossil fuels and petroleum date back to 3000 B.C. For
            example, Persian chemists invented modern day napalm by mixing petroleum
            with quicklime called “Greek Fire”. Coal goes back even further into history. “Coal,
            scientists believe, was used sporadically by cave people”. Native Americans used
            coal to bake clay pottery. Coal and petroleum both saw major inclines in usage
            many years later during the “Industrial Age”. The invention of the Steam-Engine
            demanded large amounts of coal that pioneers in early stages of America began
            to mine. Today, coal is mined in tons of loads across America in states such as
            Montana, West Virginia, and Kentucky.
            
            Today more energy sources are being used and developed. Hydroelectric, solar,
            wind and nuclear are some of the most popular. However, each of these sources
            have their own downside. Nuclear power has suffered from some major disasters.
            Hydroelectric power isn’t as reliable as desired mostly because of our nation’s
            geography. The most efficient hydro generators are located on rivers that are on
            
            steeper declines. The faster and larger the flow, the better the energy source. Solar
            power, similarly, are best in locations of flat and hot lands like deserts. The largest
            location of solar panels in America are in the Mojave Desert. Wind Power is best in
            the Mid-West. Indiana, Iowa, Missouri, and the Dakotas.
            
            Continuing to develop energy sources will be crucial both to our country and the
            world in the next decades.
            </description>
    </content>
    
    <content>
        <contentType>next</contentType>
        <thumbnail>next.png</thumbnail>
    </content>
    
</module>
