<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<module>
    <id>6</id>
    <title>Carbon Capture and Storage</title>
    <content>
        <page>6</page>
        <contentType>video</contentType>
        <thumbnail>Carbon_Capture_Storage.png</thumbnail>
        <url>https://www.youtube.com/v/FrpJBrHMZXs?version=3</url>
        <description>Carbon is a significant issue in the energy industry. There are two major areas of research in how to manage carbon: the storage of carbon and the use of carbon to create biofuels.</description>
    </content>
    <content>
        <contentType>image</contentType>
        <thumbnail>Photos.png</thumbnail>
        <caption_image>Carbon Capture, Storage and...Biomass image 2.jpg</caption_image>
        <description>Researchers at the University of Kentucky experiment with growing biomass to reduce CO2 emissions from burning coal.  Exposing algae to CO2 and sunlight causes the algae population to explode.</description>
    </content>
    <content>
        <contentType>text</contentType>
        <thumbnail>More_Info.png</thumbnail>
        <description>
            Carbon Capture and Storage
            
            The most obvious constraint on carbon emissions arises from climate change.
            Burning fossil fuels accounts for about three-fourths of the anthropogenic carbon
            dioxide emitted in the US. While all fossil fuels contain carbon, coal is the most
            carbon-intensive, putting coal at a disadvantage in a carbon-controlled world.
            Because electricity generation is the single largest contributor to carbon emissions
            and over half of the electricity generated in the US is from coal, there is a pressing
            need to develop viable carbon-control technologies, which can be implemented in a
            practical and affordable manner.
            
            There are three ways to reduce carbon emissions from electricity generation. The
            first and best method is to use energy more efficiently to reduce our needs from
            fossil fuel combustion. Another way is to increase our supply from renewable, low-
            carbon, and carbon-free energy. The third is to separate, capture and securely store
            carbon dioxide (i.e., carbon sequestration).
            
            Biomass can be converted by thermal or biological routes into various forms of
            energy including process heat, steam, motive power, and electricity, as well as liquid
            fuels, chemicals and synthesis gas. However, biomass feedstocks have economic
            deficiencies that we must overcome if they are to be viable. The low density and
            high water content of biomass makes shipping costs prohibitive in many cases, yet
            
            most subsequent refining processes require centralized facilities, where large-scale
            operations greatly increase process efficiencies.
            
        </description>
    </content>
    
    <content>
        <contentType>next</contentType>
        <thumbnail>next.png</thumbnail>
    </content>

</module>